ILR School Term Paper File /3077
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
ILR School Term Paper File
1948-1983
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation & Archives
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations (NYSSILR)
/3077
6 cubic feet
6 linear ft.
Records (documents).
A collection of the better term papers written by students in labor union history and collective bargaining.
3080208
General
Contact Information:
Kheel Center for Labor-Management Documentation and Archives Martin P. Catherwood Library 227 Ives Hall Cornell University Ithaca, NY 14853 (607) 255-3183 kheel_center@cornell.edu http://www.ilr.cornell.edu/library/kheel-center
Compiled by:
R. Miles, January 12, 2016
EAD encoding:
Kheel Staff, February 22, 2019
Conditions Governing Access
Access to the collections in the Kheel Center is restricted. Please contact a reference archivist for access to these materials.
Related Materials
Related Collections: /3001: Jean T. McKelvey Papers /3007: Maurice Neufeld Papers /3012: Alice Cook Papers /3035: Eric Polisar Papers /3065: ILR School Extension Division Records
New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations.; New York State School of Industrial and Labor Relations --Students.
3080208
- Abbott, Edward P., 1960 (Box 1, Folder 1)
- Abramowitz, Sandra, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 2)
- Abrams, et al., 1951 (Box 1, Folder 3)
- Airy, M., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 4)
- Alpern, Jerome, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 5)
- Alter, Ida, 1983 (Box 1, Folder 6)
- Alvy, Norman D., 1966 (Box 1, Folder 7)
- Ames, Robert J., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 8)
- Arneson, Howard (term paper), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 9)
- Axelrod, Jon P., 1965 (Box 1, Folder 10)
- Babcock, George, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 11)
- Babcock, George (Box 1, Folder 12)
- Babiskin, William, 1968 (Box 1, Folder 13)
- Bachner, Jane H., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 14)
- Bacon, John W. (Box 1, Folder 15)
- Bailey, Robert B. (Box 1, Folder 16)
- Baird, R., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 17)
- The Legal Aspects of Featherbedding, 1964 (Box 1, Folder 18)
- Bales, M. (term paper), 1964 (Box 1, Folder 19)
- Balsara, T.P. (term paper), 1957 (Box 1, Folder 20)
- Barkham, Graham, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 21)
- Barriere, Lionel (term paper), 1956 (Box 1, Folder 22)
- Baulch, George and Gerald Rose (term paper), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 23)
- Bean, A. (Box 1, Folder 24)
- Beaudoin, Guy (Box 1, Folder 25)
- Belasco, James Allan, 1965 (Box 1, Folder 26)
- Bemis, Lloyd E. Jr., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 27)
- Berger, William H., 1970 (Box 1, Folder 28)
- Bergman, Bruce, 1966 (Box 1, Folder 29)
- Bermas, Stephan, 1946 (Box 1, Folder 30)
- Birdsall, William C., 1936-1947 (Box 1, Folder 31)
- Bloom, Edwin J. -and- Thompson. Donald, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 32)
- Bloom, Leonard H., 1967 (Box 1, Folder 33)
- Blumberg, Frederick (Box 1, Folder 34)
- Boehmke, Harry F. (Box 1, Folder 35)
- Boris, Richard S. (term paper), 1961 (Box 1, Folder 36)
- Brennan, Thomas M. (Box 1, Folder 37)
- Brockman, Leonard M., 1968 (Box 1, Folder 38)
- Broderick, Walter E., 1948 (Box 1, Folder 39)
- Brookover, George (Box 1, Folder 40)
- Brown, Lawrence, 1951 (Box 1, Folder 41)
- Brown Williams, 1956 (Box 1, Folder 42)
- Bundarin, Peter (term paper), 1960 (Box 1, Folder 43)
- Burke, John, 1962-1966 (Box 1, Folder 44)
- Burns, William P. (Box 1, Folder 45)
- Button, W.H., 1963 (Box 1, Folder 46)
- Carlin, John, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 1)
- Carney, Robert W., 1950 (Box 2, Folder 2)
- Carinci, Franco, 1955 (Box 2, Folder 3)
- Chabora, Michael, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 4)
- Chambers, Sonya, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 5)
- Ciluffo, Francis A., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 6)
- Cordova, Efren, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 7)
- Court, A. (Box 2, Folder 8)
- Crane, R., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 9)
- Crisara, R. (Box 2, Folder 10)
- Culverhouse, Edward F., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 11)
- Curtin, Edward, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 12)
- D'andrea, Jr., A., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 13)
- Depew, Calvin R. (Box 2, Folder 14)
- Dinwoodie, S. David, 1957 (Box 2, Folder 15)
- Disini, Domingo P. (Box 2, Folder 16)
- Doering, Barbara, 1968 (Box 2, Folder 17)
- Dona, Ralph, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 18)
- The Judicial and Legislative Evolution of the Secondary Boycott, 1966 (Box 2, Folder 19)
- Downey, John V., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 20)
- Doyle, Lawrence F., 1967 (Box 2, Folder 21)
- Dropkin, Dave, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 22)
- Duffy, Edward (Box 2, Folder 23)
- Duflocq, Robert (Box 2, Folder 24)
- Dye, Joseph T., 1949 (Box 2, Folder 25)
- Eischen, Dana (Box 2, Folder 26)
- Eldrige, Paul W., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 27)
- Ellis, Norman, 1962 (Box 2, Folder 28)
- Embridge, Warren, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 29)
- Erle, Jack, 1948 (Box 2, Folder 30)
- Featherbedding and the Law, 1964 (Box 2, Folder 31)
- Erstling, Jay A., 1971 (Box 2, Folder 32)
- Evans, Robert R. (Box 2, Folder 33)
- Falkin, Jeffrey, 1965 (Box 2, Folder 34)
- Felker and Morton, 1947 (Box 2, Folder 35)
- Ferster, Bernard, 1958 (Box 2, Folder 36)
- Finder, Hopkins and Miller, 1956 (Box 2, Folder 37)
- Fisher. Joseph T., 1948 (Box 2, Folder 38)
- Fizer, Chandler F. (Box 2, Folder 39)
- Foley, John C., 1959 (Box 2, Folder 40)
- Forney, Ross, 1934 (Box 2, Folder 41)
- Fortique S, Richard, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 42)
- Foster, Howard G., 1966 (Box 2, Folder 43)
- Frankenfield, C. H. (Box 2, Folder 44)
- Frawley, R. H. (Box 2, Folder 45)
- Freeman, Michael, 1967 (Box 2, Folder 46)
- Friess, Alan (Box 2, Folder 47)
- Crocchiolo, Andrew, 1949 (Box 2, Folder 48)
- Glass, 1978 (Box 3, Folder 1)
- Gale, John (Box 3, Folder 2)
- David E. Keefe (Box 3, Folder 3)
- Klee, Thomas A., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 4)
- Kornfield, Marc, 1963 (Box 3, Folder 5)
- Garr, Myron M., 1946 (Box 3, Folder 6)
- Garton, Robert, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 7)
- Gelber, Steven, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 8)
- Gelzahler, W. (Box 3, Folder 9)
- Genung, J., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 10)
- Gilbert, H. M. Jr., 1959 (Box 3, Folder 11)
- Gilligan, Thomas, 1969 (Box 3, Folder 12)
- Glatt, Carl W., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 13)
- Goetz, S., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 14)
- Goldstein, Marvin, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 15)
- Goodwin, David, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 16)
- Goodson, W.F., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 17)
- Craney J. (Box 3, Folder 18)
- Gray, W., 1940-1946 (Box 3, Folder 19)
- Gauar, Frank H. (term paper), 1955 (Box 3, Folder 20)
- Gosseen, Robert Irvin (term paper), 1963 (Box 3, Folder 21)
- Gumpert, Jon, 1962 (Box 3, Folder 22)
- Hamburg, S. (Box 3, Folder 23)
- Hansen, Gary B., 1967 (Box 3, Folder 24)
- Hanson, Susan, 1958 (Box 3, Folder 25)
- Harrison, Vance, 1948 (Box 3, Folder 26)
- Haskell, Charles K. (Box 3, Folder 27)
- Hayes, Roger, 1964 (Box 3, Folder 28)
- Hedges, Harold C. (Box 3, Folder 29)
- Helmcke, Carol, 1966 (Box 3, Folder 30)
- Henderson, Christopher L., 1934 (Box 3, Folder 31)
- Henderson, Christopher L., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 32)
- Heptig, Richard T., 1960 (Box 3, Folder 33)
- Herman, C., 1948 (Box 3, Folder 34)
- Hines, Robert Jr. (Box 3, Folder 35)
- Hoffman, Richard B., 1966 (Box 3, Folder 36)
- Hurd, Ray and Windmuller, John (Box 3, Folder 37)
- Huret, Robert, 1965 (Box 3, Folder 38)
- Ibrahim, Mustapha, 1968-1969 (Box 4, Folder 1)
- Jackson, Carroll (term paper), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 2)
- Jackson, Carroll (term paper), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 3)
- Jacobson, Myron, 1964 (Box 4, Folder 4)
- Jaffe, joseph, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 5)
- Jones, John R. (Box 4, Folder 6)
- Kahn, Kenneth, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 7)
- Kaiser, P., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 8)
- Kane, Nancy H., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 9)
- Kaplan, Joel H., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 10)
- Kasputys, Thomas, 1966 (Box 4, Folder 11)
- Keller, Robert, 1970 (Box 4, Folder 12)
- Kendellen, Gary, 1967 (Box 4, Folder 13)
- Klein, Stuart (Box 4, Folder 14)
- Knipp, Anthony, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 15)
- Kobrin, R., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 16)
- Koenig, Joshua N., 1967 (Box 4, Folder 17)
- Kohn, Thomas H., 1969 (Box 4, Folder 18)
- Krouner, Leonard (Box 4, Folder 19)
- Lamb, John, 1936-1937 (Box 4, Folder 20)
- Lampert, Bernard P. (Box 4, Folder 21)
- Lapinsky, Martin (term paper), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 22)
- Lee, Pei, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 23)
- Leenhouts, H., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 24)
- Lefcourt, Roy V., 1966 (Box 4, Folder 25)
- Rebellion at River Rouge (Box 4, Folder 26)
- Lerner, Earle, 1948 (Box 4, Folder 27)
- Leonard, Arthur S., 1974 (Box 4, Folder 28)
- Leroy, Jr, F., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 29)
- Levine, Alan H. (Box 4, Folder 30)
- Levy, Helen, 1946 (Box 4, Folder 31)
- Levy, Richard (term paper), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 32)
- Liden, Beverly (term paper), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 33)
- Liddle. Jeffrey L., 1970 (Box 4, Folder 34)
- Lieberman, Paul (term paper), 1963 (Box 4, Folder 35)
- Lipton, Neil D. (term paper), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 36)
- Lobel, Ira, 1969 (Box 4, Folder 37)
- Locke, Charles F. (Box 4, Folder 38)
- Locke, Edwin (term paper), 1962 (Box 4, Folder 39)
- Locke, R., 1948 (Box 4, Folder 40)
- Sanford Lowe, 1956 (Box 4, Folder 41)
- David Lubell, 1951 (Box 4, Folder 42)
- Lynch, James (term paper), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 43)
- Lynch, J. (term paper), 1961 (Box 4, Folder 44)
- Madden, Robert E., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 1)
- Marcus, Averill, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 2)
- Martin, John Collier, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 3)
- McCarthy, W (Box 5, Folder 4)
- MacGregor, Jr., F. (Box 5, Folder 5)
- McFarland, D. E., 1951 (Box 5, Folder 6)
- McKenna, James J., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 7)
- McKenzie, B., 1937 (Box 5, Folder 8)
- McKierman, Gordon, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 9)
- McLeod, Hillary W. (Box 5, Folder 10)
- McNiece, Walter V., 1939 (Box 5, Folder 11)
- McQuillen, Charles D. (term paper), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 12)
- Madden, Edward J., 1873-1948 (Box 5, Folder 13)
- Madison, Herb, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 14)
- Mahoney, F. (Box 5, Folder 15)
- Marin Elias, Harry (Box 5, Folder 16)
- Marks, Fred, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 17)
- Merdes, Edward A. (Box 5, Folder 18)
- Matchulat, John Jay, 1966 (Box 5, Folder 19)
- Miller, Thomas V. (term paper), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 20)
- Minikes, Stepan M. (term paper), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 21)
- Meyn, C., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 22)
- Miller, Bernard F., 1969 (Box 5, Folder 23)
- Mintz, Herb., 1947 (Box 5, Folder 24)
- Mitchell, Theodora, 1963 (Box 5, Folder 25)
- Monat, Larry (term paper), 1963 (Box 5, Folder 26)
- Morris, Richard A. (Box 5, Folder 27)
- Morrison, R., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 28)
- Murray, Vic (term paper), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 29)
- Muth, John J. (term paper), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 30)
- Nekos, Maria, 1948 (Box 5, Folder 31)
- Newman, Morris W., 1957 (Box 5, Folder 32)
- Nichols, Cathy, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 33)
- O'regan, Robert (Box 5, Folder 34)
- Orton. Eliot (Box 5, Folder 35)
- O'Rouke, P., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 36)
- Parker, Joan, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 37)
- Peeler, Joe, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 38)
- Penski, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 39)
- Pezet, Julien A., 1965 (Box 5, Folder 40)
- Pirzio, Gloria (term paper), 1962 (Box 5, Folder 41)
- Polland, Elliot, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 42)
- Psachie. Lynda S., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 43)
- Rankey, George C. (term paper), 1961 (Box 5, Folder 44)
- Rankey, George C., 1961 (Box 5, Folder 45)
- Reitkopp, Howard H. (term paper), 1973 (Box 5, Folder 46)
- Rimicci, Ross A., 1970 (Box 5, Folder 47)
- Ripley, N., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 48)
- Rodgers. William, 1964 (Box 5, Folder 49)
- Rodgers, William, 1961 (Box 5, Folder 50)
- Romero, J., 1948 (Box 5, Folder 51)
- Rosen, Sidney, 1970 (Box 5, Folder 52)
- Rosenzweig, Stefan, 1965 (Box 5, Folder 53)
- Ross, Mitchel S., 1966 (Box 5, Folder 54)
- Rowland, Clifford Part 1, 1950 (Box 5, Folder 55)
- Rowland, Clifford Part 2, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 56)
- Rowland Clifford Part 3, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 57)
- Rowland, Clifford Part 4 (Box 5, Folder 58)
- Rumsey - Mitchell - Hoblock, 1956 (Box 5, Folder 59)
- Ryan, Joseph (Box 5, Folder 60)
- Salsberg, Richard M., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 1)
- Savelson, Donald, 1963 (Box 6, Folder 2)
- Schimel, Ruth M. (term paper), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 3)
- Schmidt, Charles T., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 4)
- Schnapp, Roger H., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 5)
- Schneider, Steven M., 1970 (Box 6, Folder 6)
- Schumacher, Lois (term paper), 1956 (Box 6, Folder 7)
- Scott, Leonard C., 1963 (Box 6, Folder 8)
- Seidenberg, J., 1945-1946 (Box 6, Folder 9)
- Scully, Marie-Celeste, 1969 (Box 6, Folder 10)
- Shamberg, Stuart R. (Box 6, Folder 11)
- Procedural Outline, 1960 (Box 6, Folder 12)
  Scope and Contents
  Bound
- Shaw, I. B., 1950 (Box 6, Folder 13)
- Sheenan, Joseph (Box 6, Folder 14)
- Sheinkman, J. (Box 6, Folder 15)
- Sington, Fred Jr. (Box 6, Folder 16)
- Smith, D. Dean (term paper), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 17)
- Smith, James C., 1957 (Box 6, Folder 18)
- Smith, Neal H., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 19)
- Smith, Robert J., 1965 (Box 6, Folder 20)
- Smith, Ronald H. (term paper), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 21)
- Spalding, Jr., W., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 22)
- Squire, Richard M., 1962 (Box 6, Folder 23)
- Stark, Jeffrey, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 24)
- Stark, Jeffrey M., 1964 (Box 6, Folder 25)
- Stedge, R. (Box 6, Folder 26)
- Stein, David, 1968 (Box 6, Folder 27)
- Stetson, Donald G. (Box 6, Folder 28)
- Stone, Victor D. L., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 29)
- Stone, Wendell, 1971 (Box 6, Folder 30)
- Stross, Peter A. (Box 6, Folder 31)
- Sultan-Kahn, S.G.A., 1967 (Box 6, Folder 32)
- Szarejko, John (term paper), 1961 (Box 6, Folder 33)
- Tarneja, Ram (Box 6, Folder 34)
- Tarr, William L. (Box 6, Folder 35)
- Taylor, Robert, 1949 (Box 6, Folder 36)
- Tessler, Daniel (term paper), 1963 (Box 6, Folder 37)
- Thomson, A.W.J., 1966 (Box 6, Folder 38)
- Thomson, A.W.J. (Box 6, Folder 39)
- Uhlinger, James R., 1956 (Box 6, Folder 40)
- Ungar, Marc, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 41)
- Vassiere, E., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 42)
- Vasse, Louis L. (Box 6, Folder 43)
- Vorhees, C., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 44)
- Voorhees, Craig, 1948 (Box 6, Folder 45)
- Waks, Jay W., 1968 (Box 6, Folder 46)
- Walker, William P., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 47)
- Weidberg, Bertrand, 1962 (Box 6, Folder 48)
- Ward, Betty A., 1947 (Box 6, Folder 49)
- 'This is an Amalgamated Local 169 (Box 6, Folder 50)
- Wells, Lee, 1964 (Box 6, Folder 51)
- Winter, Robert J., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 52)
- Yuan, Edw., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 53)
- Zibel, Howard (Box 6, Folder 54)
- Zimmerman, William (Box 6, Folder 55)
- Zitowsky, W., 1948 (Box 6, Folder 56)
- Zloth, S., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 57)
- Zloth, S., 1949 (Box 6, Folder 57)